{
  "cards": [
    {
      "name": "Basic Simple",
      "imageFront": "basic_set",
      "imageBack": "cards_basicskin_drawable",
      "description": "card1_description",
      "prix": "Free",
      "estAchetee": true,
      "rarete": "Common",
      "selected": true,
      "default": true
    },
    {
      "name": "Free",
      "imageFront": "basic_set",
      "imageBack": "cards_basicskin2_drawable",
      "description": "card2_description",
      "prix": "Free",
      "estAchetee": false,
      "rarete": "Common",
      "selected": false,
      "default": false
    },
    {
      "name": "Le Zoo",
      "imageFront": "zoo_set",
      "imageBack": "cards_zoo_drawable",
      "description": "card3_description",
      "prix": "999 999 999 999 999,99",
      "estAchetee": false,
      "rarete": "Unique",
      "selected": false,
      "default": false
    },
    {
      "name": "3ario",
      "imageFront": "basic_set",
      "imageBack": "cards_mario_drawable",
      "description": "card4_description",
      "prix": "3,33",
      "estAchetee": false,
      "rarete": "Uncommon",
      "selected": false,
      "default": false
    },
    {
      "name": "Suber Sonig Bros.",
      "imageFront": "basic_set",
      "imageBack": "cards_sonic_drawable",
      "description": "card5_description",
      "prix": "4,99",
      "estAchetee": false,
      "rarete": "Uncommon",
      "selected": false,
      "default": false
    },
    {
      "name": "Density",
      "imageFront": "basic_set",
      "imageBack": "cards_density_drawable",
      "description": "card6_description",
      "prix": "29,99999",
      "estAchetee": false,
      "rarete": "Rare",
      "selected": false,
      "default": false
    },
    {
      "name": "Overmatch",
      "imageFront": "basic_set",
      "imageBack": "cards_overmatch_drawable",
      "description": "card7_description",
      "prix": "39.99",
      "estAchetee": false,
      "rarete": "Rare",
      "selected": false,
      "default": false
    },
    {
      "name": "Call of Bounty",
      "imageFront": "basic_set",
      "imageBack": "cards_call_of_bounty_drawable",
      "description": "card8_description",
      "prix": "39.99",
      "estAchetee": false,
      "rarete": "Rare",
      "selected": false,
      "default": false
    },
    {
      "name": "Spooder-Man into the Spooder-Verse",
      "imageFront": "basic_set",
      "imageBack": "cards_spooderman_drawable",
      "description": "card9_description",
      "prix": "89.99",
      "estAchetee": false,
      "rarete": "Epic",
      "selected": false,
      "default": false
    },
    {
      "name": "Valoriant",
      "imageFront": "basic_set",
      "imageBack": "cards_valoriant_drawable",
      "description": "card10_description",
      "prix": "14.99",
      "estAchetee": false,
      "rarete": "Uncommon",
      "selected": false,
      "default": false
    },
    {
      "name": "The Legend of Zaldo",
      "imageFront": "basic_set",
      "imageBack": "cards_zaldo_drawable",
      "description": "card11_description",
      "prix": "11.99",
      "estAchetee": false,
      "rarete": "Uncommon",
      "selected": false,
      "default": false
    },
    {
      "name": "Dooooom",
      "imageFront": "basic_set",
      "imageBack": "cards_dooooom_drawable",
      "description": "card12_description",
      "prix": "13.99",
      "estAchetee": false,
      "rarete": "Uncommon",
      "selected": false,
      "default": false
    }
  ]
}

